GURRAPU SAISREEJA



Address:

Flat No: 1-10-189/301, Padmalaya Residence, Hyderabad.

Phone:

+919032441421

Email:

saisreejagurrapu@gmail.com

Languages

- English
- Telugu
- Hindi

Summary

ETL Tester specializing in testing data from source to target. Experienced with all stages of the testing data for dynamic projects deliverables. Well-versed in writing SQL queries based ontransformations simple and complex using databases MySQL, Oracle.

SkillHighlights

- ETLTesting
- SQL
- TestCasePreparation
- DatabaseTesting
- Datawarehouse
- Oracle
- Regression Testing
- Re-Testing

Experience

- Having4.11yearsofprofessionallTexperienceinETLtesting/Da tabasetesting,UITestingworkedonvariousdomains— Insurance, Retail.
- GoodknowledgeonETLProcess, Datawarehousing, Database Concepts using Informatica, PL/SQL Developer, OracleSQLDeveloper, SQLServer Management Studio, Netezza, Azure Databricks, Snowflake Database, SapHana.
- Expertise in writing test cases and testing the test scenariosintoolsHP-ALMTestManagement,AzureDatabricks,Jira.
- Strongworkingknowledgeon**EndtoEndDefectlifeCycle** ManagementusingHP-ALM.
- GoodexperienceinOLTP &OLAP.
- Extensive work experience in Initial and Incremental LoadTestingasPartof SystemIntegrationTesting.
- GoodexperienceonStarandSnowflakes Schemas.
- Strong knowledge of Slowly Changing Dimensions (SCD-2)Testing &GoodKnowledgeofUNIXcommands.

Education

MBAFinancefromJAWAHARLALNEHRUTECHNOLOGICALUNIVERSITY Hyderabadin 2017

Professional Experience

Working as Consultant in Virtusa Consulting Services pvt ltd from May 2021 to till date.

Worked as Software Engineer in Wipro Itd from July 2017 to May 2021.



Professional Experience

Project: 3

ProjectName :CHUBB

• IndustryandBusinessofClient :HealthServices

Duration :Feb2020 toMar2021

Tools& :Ab Initio, Oracle SQL Developer, SQL

ServerManagementStudio,Netezza,AzureDatab

ricks

Role :TestEngineer

• TeamSize :3

Description:

Chubb Limited is an American company incorporated in Zürich, Switzerland, is the parent company of Chubb, aglobal provider of insurance products covering property and casualty, accident and health, reinsurance, and lifeinsurance and the largest publicly traded property and Casualty Company in the world. Chubb operates in 55countries and territories and in the Lloyd's insurance market in London. Clients of Chubb consist of multinational corporations and local businesses, individuals, and insurers seeking reinsurance coverage.

Responsibilities:

- Preparation of Testscenarios to coverentire datavalidation between different layers.
- Workingexperienceon Snowflakeschemaandvalidationofdimensionsandfacttables.
- ExperienceinRegressiontesting,SanityTesting,BoundaryvalueTesting.
- VerifyingAuditFields&Emailnotifications.
- RaisingtheDefectswhileexecutingtheInitialandIncrementalloadTesting.
- InvolvedinDefectTriageMeetings.
- WritingtherequiredSQLQueriestoverifythedatabetweendifferentdatabases.
- Preparation of Test Data to Perform Incremental load Testing.
- Nullchecks, duplicates checks and tables count checks.

Project: 2

• Project Name : Excellus

Industry and BusinessofClient : Healthcare Insurance Services

Duration : Apr2021 to till date

Tools

:Informatica,PL/SQLDeveloper, PegaCDHWebapplication

Role :TestEngineer

• TeamSize :3

Description:

Excellus BlueCross BlueShield (Excellus,BCBS or Excellus) is a non-profit health insurance company headquarteredin Rochester, New York. It is part of the Blue Cross Blue Shield Association. Excellus BCBS is upstate New York'slargestnonprofit health plan.

Responsibilities:

- Preparation of Testscenarios to coverentire PEGA testing & ETLT esting.
- Writingthe requiredSQLQueries to verify the data from file to CDHApplications.
- PreparationofTestDatatoinsertdataintolandingtablestovalidateendto endscenarios.
- VerifyingPEGAWebapplicationasperbusinessrequirements.
- ExperienceinprocessingtestdataintoAddresstablesthroughDATAVOLVE.
- ExperienceinworkingonAddressdata&customerdataprocessingthroughDATAFLUXstudio.
- ExperienceinRegressiontesting,SanityTesting,BoundaryvalueTesting.
- VerifyingAuditFields&Emailnotifications.
- RaisingthedefectswhileperformingbothETL&PEGATesting.

Project: 1

ProjectName :LOYDS(LBG)
 IndustryandBusinessofClient :BANKDOMAIN
 Duration :Nov2017toJan2019

Tools& :POWERBI

Role :POWERDEVELOPER

• TeamSize :3

Description:

The bank merged first with the newly demutualised Cheltenham & Gloucester Building Society, then with the TSBGroup in 1995. The C&G acquisition gave Lloyds a large stake in the UK mortgage lending market. The TSB mergerwas structured as a reverse takeover; Lloyds Bank Plc was delisted from the London Stock Exchange and TSB Group plc was renamed Lloyds TSB Group plc on 28 December, with former Lloyds Bank shareholders owning a 70% equityinterest in the share capital, effected through a scheme of arrangement. TSB Bank plc transferred engagements to Lloyds Bank Plc which then changed its name to Lloyds TSB Bank plc; at the same time, TSB Bank Scotland plcabsorbedLloyds'threeScottishbranches becomingLloydsTSB Scotlandplc.

Responsibilities:

- Proficientatdatavisualizationusing PowerBlandastrongapplication development.
- GoodExperienceonImplementationofRowLevelSecuritybydefiningvariousconstraintsforeachdefine dROLE.
- ExpertcreatingdifferentvisualizationsusingSlicers, Lines, Pies, Histograms, Maps, Scatter,
 Treemaps, etc.
- MaintainingandSupportingoperationalreports, dashboards, and scorecards using Microsoft Power BI.
- Having good Experience in creating dashboards, volume reports, operating summariesandgraphs.
- Expert in publishing reports to app.powerbi.com and setting up the necessary connection detailsand scheduling.

Declaration

Iherebydeclarethatalltheinformationfurnishedaboveistruetothebestofmyknowledge.